let questions = [
    {
      question: "How many rings of power were made for the Elves?",
      choice1: "7",
      choice2: "4",
      choice3: "3",
      choice4: "9",
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Fellowship comprised of?",
      choice1: "2 Hobbits, 5 Men, 1 Elf and 1 Wizard ",
      choice2: "3 Hobbits, 2 Men, 1 Elf, 1 Dwarf and 1 Wizard",
      choice3: "4 Hobbits, 2 Men, 1 Elf, 2 Dwarves and 1 Wizard",
      choice4: "4 Hobbits, 2 Men, 1 Elf, 1 Dwarf and 1 Wizard ",
      answer: 4
    },
    {
      question: "Who did Frodo receive a shirt of mithril from?",
      choice1: "Gandalf",
      choice2: "Bilbo",
      choice3: "Boromir",
      choice4: "Aragorn",
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What color is Bilbo's door?",
      choice1: "Green",
      choice2: "Yellow",
      choice3: "Red",
      choice4: "Blue",
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "What is the subtitle of the second LOTR book?",
      choice1: "The Two Towers",
      choice2: "The Fellowship of the Ring",
      choice3: "The Return of the King",
      choice4: "Silmarillion",
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "What is Wormtongueâ€™s real name?",
      choice1: "Lotho",
      choice2: "Larma",
      choice3: "Grima",
      choice4: "Dourif",
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the giant spider who tried to eat Frodo?",
      choice1: "Balrog",
      choice2: "Morgoth",
      choice3: "Shelob",
      choice4: "Ungoliant",
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "How many rings of power were made in total?",
      choice1: "7",
      choice2: "9",
      choice3: "20",
      choice4: "10",
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "What birthday does Bilbo Baggins celebrate in the Fellowship of the Ring?",
      choice1: "111th",
      choice2: "89th",
      choice3: "94th",
      choice4: "120th",
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Which army does Aragorn end up convincing to help them fight Sauron?",
      choice1: "The Ents",
      choice2: "The Dead",
      choice3: "The Corsairs of Umbar",
      choice4: "The Eagles",
      answer: 2
    },
  ];